Finding Aid for Men's Glee Club (University of Michigan) records 1886-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Annual Spring Concert, 1955 May 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-9-1-1]; mp3 file; (University of Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Now Thank We All Our God; Hymn to the Eternal; Good Fellows Be Merry; 3 piano numbers; Vagabond; In the Silence of the Night; Is my Team Plowing; My Good Old Man; The Pirate; Gabriel Blow Your Horn; What Was the Matter with Rachmaninoff?; Lullaby of Birdland; There is a Balm in Gilead; Sing Something Simple.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & University of Illinois Varsity Glee Club Combined Concert, 1956 November 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-10-1-1]; mp3 file; (Illinois Glee Club performs: The God Who Gave Us Life Gave Us Liberty, The Shepherdess, Die Minnesanger, Three Male Choruses, Little Thora, There Is No Folly Half So Great, Kvaalin's Halling, The Constant Cannibal Maiden,Tit for Tat, Pirate Song, Marry a Woman Uglier Than You, There is Nothing Like a Dame, Hail to the Orange, Hail To The Blue. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina, Who is Sylvia, Fine Knacks for Ladies, The Heart Worships, Eileen, Lay Down Doggies, County Fair (Featuring the Novelaires) Selections by the Friars: Michigan Songs, The Bum Army; The Old Friars Songs; Goddess of the Inland Seas, Victors. Alma Maters: We're Loyal To You Illinois; The Yellow and Blue by Combined Glee Clubs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "Miscellaneous College Songs", 1957 June 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-11-1-1]; mp3 file; (University of Michigan Men's Glee Club performing: Whiffenpoof Song; Hail to California; Colorado; Hail to Our Alma Mater; Oregon; Amherst; Army; Navy; Columbia; Cornell; GA Tech; Notre Dame; Wisconsin; Texas.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 99th Annual Spring Concert, 1958 May 10; 5 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips (Box 9)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-12-1-1]; mp3 file; (5 reels) several copies of the same concert. Part 1; Michigan Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress Is Our God; O Magnum Mysterium; Tobacco; Come Let's Be Merry; Phantasiestucke (Schumann); Prelude in B Flat Major Op.23 Rachmaninoff; Night and Dreams; Let Beauty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heavens; Lord Randall; Great Day; Romance; Love Is Where You Find It; Easy to Love; In the Still of the Night; I'm Gettin' Sentimental Over You; I've Never Benn in Love Before; Ah! Sweet Mystery of Life; Selections by the Friars; (Michigan Songs) Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast To Michigan; I Wanna Go Back To Michigan; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; Michigan Men; Goddess of the Inland Seas; The Friars Song; The Bum Army; When Night Falls, Dear; Varsity; The Old Friars Song; The Victors; Yellow and Blue.
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-12-2-1]; mp3 file; ((5 reels. # 4-5 not digittized) several copies of the same concert. Part 2; Michigan Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress Is Our God; O Magnum Mysterium; Tobacco; Come Let's Be Merry; Phantasiestucke (Schumann); Prelude in B Flat Major Op.23 Rachmaninoff; Night and Dreams; Let Beauty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heavens; Lord Randall; Great Day; Romance; Love Is Where You Find It; Easy to Love; In the Still of the Night; I'm Gettin' Sentimental Over You; I've Never Benn in Love Before; Ah! Sweet Mystery of Life; Selections by the Friars; (Michigan Songs) Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast To Michigan; I Wanna Go Back To Michigan; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; Michigan Men; Goddess of the Inland Seas; The Friars Song; The Bum Army; When Night Falls, Dear; Varsity; The Old Friars Song; The Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-12-3-1]; mp3 file; ((5 reels. # 4-5 not digittized) several copies of the same concert. Part 3; Michigan Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress Is Our God; O Magnum Mysterium; Tobacco; Come Let's Be Merry; Phantasiestucke (Schumann); Prelude in B Flat Major Op.23 Rachmaninoff; Night and Dreams; Let Beauty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heavens; Lord Randall; Great Day; Romance; Love Is Where You Find It; Easy to Love; In the Still of the Night; I'm Gettin' Sentimental Over You; I've Never Benn in Love Before; Ah! Sweet Mystery of Life; Selections by the Friars; (Michigan Songs) Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast To Michigan; I Wanna Go Back To Michigan; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; Michigan Men; Goddess of the Inland Seas; The Friars Song; The Bum Army; When Night Falls, Dear; Varsity; The Old Friars Song; The Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "The Pat Boone Show", 1958 May 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-13-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 1; Recording of Men's Glee Club on the Pat Boone show.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, Michigan Songs, 1958 July 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-14-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Glee Club performs Michigan Songs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast to Michigan; I Wanna go Back to Michigan; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; Drink, Drink, Joy Rules the Day; Michigan Men; When Night Falls; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Ann Arbor Days; The Bum Army; The Old Friars' Song; Varsity.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-14-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Men's Glee Club performs Concert Songs; Invocation of Orpheus from "Euridice", Peri); Now Thank We All Our God (Crger); Hallelujah, Amen (from "Judas Maccabaeus", Handel); Tobacco (Hume); Good Fellows, Be Merry (Bach); There Is a Balm in Gilead (Dan Pressley, tenor, Spiritual); My Good Old Man (Kentucky Mountain Song); Clementine (Montrose); Casey Jones (American Folk Song).)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, Michigan Songs, 1958 July 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Indiana University Singing Hoosiers Combined Concert, 1958 November 15; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-16-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Indiana Hoosiers sing: With a Song in My Heart For You, Dream While You're Feeling Blue, Candy Dancer's Ball, More, I Cannot Wish You, Graduation Days, Manhattan Towers; I Believe; My Fair Lady. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Invocation of Orpheus; Come My Beloved; To The Women; The Omnipotence; There is a Balm in Gilead; Eileen; We Three; Lullaby of Birdland; Luck be a Lady. Selections by the Friars of Michigan Songs: Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast To Michigan, I Wanna Go Back To Michigan, I'll Never Forget My College Days, Featuring the Midnight Sons; The Old Friars Song, Presentation to Alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by President Harlan Hatcher, Drink, Drink, Joy Rules the Day; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Hymn, Written Especially for our Centennial; The Victors; The Alma Maters - Hail to Old I.U., The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-16-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Indiana Hoosiers sing: With a Song in My Heart For You, Dream While You're Feeling Blue, Candy Dancer's Ball, More, I Cannot Wish You, Graduation Days, Manhattan Towers; I Believe; My Fair Lady. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Invocation of Orpheus; Come My Beloved; To The Women; The Omnipotence; There is a Balm in Gilead; Eileen; We Three; Lullaby of Birdland; Luck be a Lady. Selections by the Friars of Michigan Songs: Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast To Michigan, I Wanna Go Back To Michigan, I'll Never Forget My College Days, Featuring the Midnight Sons; The Old Friars Song, Presentation to Alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by President Harlan Hatcher, Drink, Drink, Joy Rules the Day; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Hymn, Written Especially for our Centennial; The Victors; The Alma Maters - Hail to Old I.U., The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 101st Annual Spring Concert, 1960 May 14; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-17-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Confitemini Domino; El Grillo; Hallelujah, Amen; Ave Maria; Non Piu Andrei; Song of Joy; Sing, Maiden, Sing; I Hear An Army; The Song of Green Mansions; The Boatmen's Dance; Blow, Gabriel, Blow; Stomp Your Foot; Jimmy Brown. And The Night Shall Be Filled With Music; Stardust; Dream; Deep Purple; Laura; Did You Ever See a Dream Walking; In The Still of The Night; The Most Beautiful Girl In The World; Selections; Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-17-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Confitemini Domino; El Grillo; Hallelujah, Amen; Ave Maria; Non Piu Andrei; Song of Joy; Sing, Maiden, Sing; I Hear An Army; The Song of Green Mansions; The Boatmen's Dance; Blow, Gabriel, Blow; Stomp Your Foot; Jimmy Brown. And The Night Shall Be Filled With Music; Stardust; Dream; Deep Purple; Laura; Did You Ever See a Dream Walking; In The Still of The Night; The Most Beautiful Girl In The World; Selections; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & University of Illinois Glee Club Combined Concert, 1960 November 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-18-1-1]; mp3 file; (Illinois Glee Club performs Alleluia For Unto Us a Child is Born; Gratias Agimus Tibi; Faire, If You Expect Admiring; Turne Backe You Wanton Flyer; Drinking Song; He's Gone Away; Go Down, Death; Soon Ah Will Be Done; Medley of Big Ten Songs. The Michigan Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; Music Will Calm Thee; Chorus of Returning Pilgrims; Good Fellows Be Merry; The Vagabond; Little Brown Jug; C# Mior Prelude Rachmaninoff; (Friars) And The Night Shall Be Filled With Music; Stardust; Dream; Deep Purple; Laura; Did You Ever See A Dream Walking; In The Still of The Night; The Most Beautiful Girl In The World; Michigan Songs; (Alma Maters) Illinois Loyalty; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 102nd Annual Spring Concert, 1961 May 13; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-19-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; Music Will Calm Thee; Mighty Spirit; Echo Song; Heigh Ho For A Husband; Good Fellows Be Merry; Gigue; Ondine; The Vagabond; The Heart Worships; Money, O1; Far Above The Purple Hills; Ain' Got Time To Die; Speak To Me Of Love; What Is This Thing Called Love?; Love Is The Sweetest Thing; Love Is a Many Splendored Thing; Love Is A Simple Thing; Would You Like To Take a Walk; Strange Music; I Met a Girl; Soft Lights and Sweet Music; 'S Wonderful, 'S Marvelous; Our Love Is Here To Stay; Love Is Sweeping The Country; The Friars selections; Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-19-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Men's Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; Music Will Calm Thee; Mighty Spirit; Echo Song; Heigh Ho For A Husband; Good Fellows Be Merry; Gigue; Ondine; The Vagabond; The Heart Worships; Money, O1; Far Above The Purple Hills; Ain' Got Time To Die; Speak To Me Of Love; What Is This Thing Called Love?; Love Is The Sweetest Thing; Love Is a Many Splendored Thing; Love Is A Simple Thing; Would You Like To Take a Walk; Strange Music; I Met a Girl; Soft Lights and Sweet Music; 'S Wonderful, 'S Marvelous; Our Love Is Here To Stay; Love Is Sweeping The Country; The Friars selections; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Duke University Glee Club Combined Concert, 1961 November 04; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-20-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Duke University's Glee Club performs Sacred Concert; Cantate Domino; When His Loud Voice In Thunder Spoke; Tarantella; The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; Casey Jones; Black Is The Color of My True Love's Hair; Poor Man Lazarus; and a selection of Michigan songs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Come, Let's Be Merry; Echo Song; The Heart Worships; Money, O!; Ain' Got Time To Die; (Friars) Selections; Speak To Me of Love; What Is This Thing Called Love?; Love Is The Sweetest Thing; Love Is a Many Splendored Thing; Love Is A Simple Thing; Would You Like To Take a Walk?; Strange Music; I Met A Girl; Soft Lights and Sweet Music; 'S Wonderful, 'S Marvelous; Our Love Is Here To Stay; Love Is Sweeping The Country; Michigan Songs; (The Alma Maters) Dear Ole Duke; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-20-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Duke University's Glee Club performs Sacred Concert; Cantate Domino; When His Loud Voice In Thunder Spoke; Tarantella; The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; Casey Jones; Black Is The Color of My True Love's Hair; Poor Man Lazarus; and a selection of Michigan songs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Come, Let's Be Merry; Echo Song; The Heart Worships; Money, O!; Ain' Got Time To Die; (Friars) Selections; Speak To Me of Love; What Is This Thing Called Love?; Love Is The Sweetest Thing; Love Is a Many Splendored Thing; Love Is A Simple Thing; Would You Like To Take a Walk?; Strange Music; I Met A Girl; Soft Lights and Sweet Music; 'S Wonderful, 'S Marvelous; Our Love Is Here To Stay; Love Is Sweeping The Country; Michigan Songs; (The Alma Maters) Dear Ole Duke; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 103rd Annual Spring Concert, 1962 May 12; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-22-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Songs performed by the Glee Club are: Laudes Atque Carmina; Come, Let's Be Merry; The Minstrel Boy; Shall I Sue?; Domine, Non Sum Dignus; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Sarabande; Prelude; The Cherubic Hymn; In the Silence of the Night; Witness; Green Leaves of Summer; With A Little Bit O'Luck; Gershwin Medley - Clap-a Yo Hands; Somebody Loves Me; Nobody But You; S'Wonderful, S'Marvelous; Who Cares?; Soon; Strike Up The Band; I Got Rhythm. The Friars perform selections of Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-22-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Songs performed by the Glee Club are: Laudes Atque Carmina; Come, Let's Be Merry; The Minstrel Boy; Shall I Sue?; Domine, Non Sum Dignus; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Sarabande; Prelude; The Cherubic Hymn; In the Silence of the Night; Witness; Green Leaves of Summer; With A Little Bit O'Luck; Gershwin Medley - Clap-a Yo Hands; Somebody Loves Me; Nobody But You; S'Wonderful, S'Marvelous; Who Cares?; Soon; Strike Up The Band; I Got Rhythm. The Friars perform selections of Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Pressing Master, 1962 June 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1,Part 1], [87250-SR-23-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Michigan Men's Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; Come, Let's Be Merry; The Minstrel Boy; Shall I Sue; Domine, Non Sum Dignus; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Cherubic Hymn; In The Silence of The Night; Witness; Green Leaves of Summer.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-23-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Men's Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; Come, Let's Be Merry; The Minstrel Boy; Shall I Sue; Domine, Non Sum Dignus; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Cherubic Hymn; In The Silence of The Night; Witness; Green Leaves of Summer.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, University Choir, and University of Michigan All-State Choir, 1962 October 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-24-1-1]; mp3 file; (Salvation Is Created; Motet form Psalm 51; A Psalm of Praise; Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Domine, non sum dignus; Michigan Songs -- Medley; Green Leaves of Summer; Ain't Got Time to Die; God is with Us; I Heard a Great Voice; Wondrous Cool, Thou Woodland Quiet; Ching-a-Ring Chaw; Song of Mary; He is Born; Set Down, Servant; Kyrie eleison; Anthem for Spring.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & University of Wisconsin Glee Club Combine Concert, 1962 November 03; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-25-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; University of Wisconsin performs Hallelujah, Amen; Jesu, Priceless Treasure; Create In Me, O God, A Pure Heart; O Magnum Mysterium; Brother Will, Brother John; Tee Roo; Highlights From South Pacific, Bail Ha'i, A Wonderful Guy, Younger Than Springtime, There Is Nothin' Like A Dame, Some Enchanted Evening; Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About The Starry Throne; Domine, Non Sum Dignus; Green Leaves of Summer; Ain't Got Time To Die; Gershwin Medley, Clap-a Yo Hands; Somebody Loves Me; Nobody But You; S'Wonderful, S'Marvelous; Who Cares?; Soon; Strike Up The Band; I Got Rhythm; Eileen; Michigan Songs; Presentation to Alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by Executive Vice President Marvin Niehuss; The Alma Maters: Wisconsin Varsity; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-25-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; University of Wisconsin performs Hallelujah, Amen; Jesu, Priceless Treasure; Create In Me, O God, A Pure Heart; O Magnum Mysterium; Brother Will, Brother John; Tee Roo; Highlights From South Pacific, Bail Ha'i, A Wonderful Guy, Younger Than Springtime, There Is Nothin' Like A Dame, Some Enchanted Evening; Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About The Starry Throne; Domine,Non Sum Dignus; Green Leaves of Summer; Ain't Got Time To Die; Gershwin Medley, Clap-a Yo Hands; Somebody Loves Me; Nobody But You; S'Wonderful, S'Marvelous; Who Cares?; Soon; Strike Up The Band; I Got Rhythm; Eileen; Michigan Songs; Presentation to Alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by Executive Vice President Marvin Niehuss; The Alma Maters: Wisconsin Varsity; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Annual Spring Concert, 1963 May 18; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-26-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; Pueri Hebraeorum; Women, What Are They?; Hymn To The Eternal; Chorus, Number 5; Etude in B Minor, Opus 25, Number 10 Chopin; The Celestial Vision Part II, White; Is My Team Plowing?; Stomp Your Foot; There Is a Balm In Gilead; The County Fair; Prologue to Pagliacci; It Ain't Necessarily So; Danza Danza; Women, What Are They?; Of Thee I Sing; I Get a Kick Out of You; Hey There; They Didn't Believe Me; All The Things You Are; And This is My Beloved; You're The Top; Thank Heaven For Little Girls. The Friars perform: My Romance, 12th St. Rag, Maria; Michigan Songs: Tis of Michigan, Drink a Toast to Michigan, I Want to go back to Michigan, I'll ne'er forget my College Days, Michigan Men - Goddess of Inland Seas, Bum Army, Old Friars Song - Varsity Victors, The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-26-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; Pueri Hebraeorum; Women, What Are They?; Hymn To The Eternal; Chorus, Number 5; Etude in B Minor, Opus 25, Number 10 Chopin; The Celestial Vision Part II, White; Is My Team Plowing?; Stomp Your Foot; There Is a Balm In Gilead; The County Fair; Prologue to Pagliacci; It Ain't Necessarily So; Danza Danza; Women, What Are They?; Of Thee I Sing; I Get a Kick Out of You; Hey There; They Didn't Believe Me; All The Things You Are; And This is My Beloved; You're The Top; Thank Heaven For Little Girls. The Friars perform: My Romance, 12th St. Rag, Maria; Michigan Songs: Tis of Michigan, Drink a Toast to Michigan, I Want to go back to Michigan, I'll ne'er forget my College Days, Michigan Men - Goddess of Inland Seas, Bum Army, Old Friars Song - Varsity Victors, The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 105th Annual Spring Concert, 1964 April 18; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-27-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; Pueri Hebraeorum; Women, What are They?; Glory to God in the Highest; Scherzo in B Minor; Songs of Travel, Part 2, Let Beauty Awake, The Infinite Shining Heaven; The Celestial Vision, Part 2 "Whitman"; Dana-Dana; She's Like a Swallow; Barnacle Bill, the Sailor; Luck be a Lady; Women, What are They? 20th Century Reprise, Medley; Of Thee I Sing; I Get a Kick Out of You; Hey There; They Didn't Believe Me; All the Things You Are; And This is My Beloved; You're The Top; Thank Heaven for Little Girls; The Friars perform a selection of Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-27-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; Pueri Hebraeorum; Women, What are They?; Glory to God in the Highest; Scherzo in B Minor; Songs of Travel, Part 2, Let Beauty Awake, The Infinite Shining Heaven; The Celestial Vision, Part 2 "Whitman"; Dana-Dana; She's Like a Swallow; Barnacle Bill, the Sailor; Luck be a Lady; Women, What are They? 20th Century Reprise, Medley; Of Thee I Sing; I Get a Kick Out of You; Hey There; They Didn't Believe Me; All the Things You Are; And This is My Beloved; You're The Top; Thank Heaven for Little Girls; The Friars perform a selection of Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Spring Concert Pressing Master, 1964 June 19; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-28-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Michigan Men's Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; Pueri Hebraeorum; Songs of Travel; The Celestial Vision; She's Like a Swallow; Luck be a Lady; Casey Jones; Hymn to Tobacco; Old Abram Brown.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-28-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Men's Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; Pueri Hebraeorum; Songs of Travel; The Celestial Vision; She's Like a Swallow; Luck be a Lady; Casey Jones; Hymn to Tobacco; Old Abram Brown.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "Chor der Singeleiter Lbeck", 1964 October 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-29-1-1]; mp3 file; (Men's Glee Club performs Theme Song, Bach - Jesu meine Freude; Mozart - Ave Verum; Bruckner - Ave Maria; Distler - Lobe den Heren; Die Singende Brucke; Aus Schottland - Loch Lomand; Aus Frankreich - La Belle Aurore; Aus Schweden - Uti Var Hage; Aus Amerika - My Fisherman; Aus Dem Baltikum - Hoch Vom Turm Zu Riga; Aus Finnland - In Deines Vaters Gartelein; Aus Deutschland - Waldensnacht; Hugo Distler - Wer Die Musik; Frliches Volkslied; East Prussia In Der Sontags Frhe; Marienlied - Auf Dem Berge Da Wehet Der Wind; Marienlied - Maria Durch Ein Dornwald Ging; Alle Birke Grunen; Helmut Brutigam - Das Orchester Deutsches Volkslied - Es Hat Ein Bauer Ein Schones Weib; Deutsches Volkslied - Beim Kronewirt Is Heute Jubel Und Tanz; Deutsches Volkslied - Der Schneider Jahrestag; Cesar Bresgau - O Du Stille Zeit.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & University of Illinois Glee Club Combine Concert, 1964 November 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips